{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"0.528/2.4",
			"answer":"0.528/2.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"204.4/0.28",
			"answer":"204.4/0.28",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"82.17/8.3",
			"answer":"82.17/8.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9.906/2.6",
			"answer":"9.906/2.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"629.8/4.7",
			"answer":"629.9/4.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.268/3.6",
			"answer":"2.268/3.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.077/0.77",
			"answer":"0.077/0.77",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"986.7/6.9",
			"answer":"986.7/6.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7950/7.5",
			"answer":"7950/7.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"79.86/0.033",
			"answer":"79.86/0.033",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}